For the Mountain View postal code 94043,
this is what the query would look like.
因为Mountain View 的邮政编码是94043，这就是查询的样子。
You could have also used
94043 comma USA and
你也能使用94043,USA 并且
that would have given
us the same result.
将会返回相同的结果。
We set the mode to be JSON format.
我们设置模式为JSON格式。
In reality, you actually don't
need this parameter because this
现实中，你完全不需要这些参数因为
API sends back JSON data by default.
API默认返回JSON格式数据。
But just to be sure,
we set this parameter.
只要确保我们设置这些参数，
Then we set the temperature
units to be in metric, and
然后我们设置温度的单位
the count param to be 7
days of forecast data.
并且要求天数为7，
Let's take this URL and
use it in our app.
让我们将这个URL放入我们的APP。